http://www.bankcardusa.com/privacy-statement/

Call Us1.800.589.8200
Protecting the privacy of users of the Virtual Application website is important to us.Our Online Privacy Statement is designed to inform you about our collection and use of personal information on this website. From time to time, BankCard USA Merchant Services Inc. (referred to in this policy as “BUSA”) may modify this Online Privacy Statement.The Online Privacy Statement is available on the home page of this website as well as at every point on the website where you provide us with personal information.If you have any questions, please contact the BankCard USA Privacy Office at cs@bankcardusa.com or (800) 589-8200.
The Only Personal Information We Collect Online is Information You Voluntarily Provide to Us.The only information we collect about you on this website is information that you voluntarily provide to us. This information may include, for example, name, mailing address, email address, phone number and similar information. If you supply us with personal information on this website, we will use that information only to contact you so that we can:- provide you with the information you have requested;- facilitate and complete merchant-initiated or authorized transactions;- comply with federal, state and local laws, including credit reporting laws and card association rules;- combat fraud; or- occasionally send you other information about BankCard USA and its services that we believe you would find interesting.
When You Browse the BankCard USA Website, You Do So Without Revealing Your Identity.This website may use cookies solely to aggregate information about the pages that users visit so that we can update and redesign, as necessary, our website in order to provide you with the most useful information. Personal information, such as your email address, is not collected unless you provide it to us. BUSA does not disclose domain name or aggregate information to third parties other than vendors who assist us with our website and who are under strict confidentiality requirements.From time to time, however, we may disclose this information to fulfill legal or regulatory obligations or if we determine such disclosure is legally advisable or necessary to protect our rights, the rights of others, or to prevent harm. In addition, we may aggregate data about users of our site and use it for statistical purposes. This information helps us to better understand our site’s users and how to improve our site and our offerings.
We Are Committed to Protecting the Confidentiality of User Information.Our policies limit access to personal user information that is collected from this website to our employees and agents and the employees and/or agents of our affiliates and business partners who need the information to fulfill their business responsibilities. BUSA may disclose personal information collected online to our affiliates and to vendors who assist us with the website. In some cases, this may require your information to be sent to other countries. By supplying your information on this website, you consent to your information being transferred across national borders to BUSA, its affiliates, vendors or agents. Vendors and other outside contractors we engage are subject to our contractual requirements for safeguarding personal information.Employees and others with duties related to this website must adhere to this Online Privacy Statement. Our employees receive annual training about the privacy policies and procedures of BankCard USA and its affiliates and subsidiaries including BUSA. We acknowledge that protecting consumer privacy is a key part of our trusted relationship with our clients.Any employee violating this Online Privacy Statement may be subject to disciplinary action, up to and including dismissal.By using this website, you agree that your use of the Virtual Application website is limited to the terms stated in your agreement with BUSA.
We Use Appropriate Security Safeguards.At BUSA, security is a priority. BUSA employs appropriate measures, including advanced technology, to protect personal information collected online against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. These measures may include, among others, encryption, physical access security, and other appropriate technologies. BUSA reviews and enhances its security systems, as necessary.
This Website is Not Directed at Persons Under the Age of 18.Our website is not directed at persons under the age of 18 and BUSA does not collect or maintain information at our website from persons we actually know are under the age of 18.
This Website May Be Linked to Other Websites.As you navigate our site, you may click to websites of our affiliated companies or business partners. Those websites may have their own online privacy statements or policies. This Online Privacy Statement will not apply when you move to one of these other sites because affiliate privacy practices and policies are tailored to the products and services offered by the individual affiliate. If you visit the pages and sites of our affiliated business units please be sure to review the privacy policies applicable to those sites.We may create links to third-party websites. BankCard USA is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by websites that are linked to from our website. BankCard USA’s privacy policies and practices do not apply to these sites. BankCard USA does not guarantee, approve, or endorse any information, material, services, or products contained on these links. BankCard USA is not responsible for any content on sites linked from or to the Virtual Application website. BankCard USA is providing the linked sites as a convenience and your connection to any linked site is at your own risk.This privacy policy only applies to the information we collect on the Virtual Application website. This privacy policy does not apply to information we collect through other methods or sources, including sites owned or operated by our affiliates, vendors or partners.
2625 Townsgate Road Suite 100       |        Westlake Village, CA 91361       |       Tel: 800.589.8200       |       Fax: 818.540.3712       |       Email: info@bankcardusa.com
BankCard USA Merchant Services is a registered ISO/MSP of Wells Fargo Bank, N.A., Concord, CA and Westamerica Bank, Santa Rosa, CA.American Express may require separate approval | Copyright ©1993-2018 BankCard USA. All Rights Reserved.Accessibility | BankCard USA’s Privacy Statement
CALL TODAY To Get Started
1.818.540.3426
Or fill out the form below with
ZERO RISK and NO OBLIGATION
A BankCard USA consultant will be in touch soon to discuss the ways we can support your business.
BankCard USA will never share or sell your information.
A BankCard USA consultant will be in touch soon to discuss the ways we can support your business.
[recaptcha]
BankCard USA will never share or sell your information.
A BankCard USA consultant will be in touch soon to discuss the ways we can support your business.
BankCard USA will never share or sell your information.
A BankCard USA consultant will be in touch soon to discuss the ways we can support your business.
BankCard USA will never share or sell your information.
A BankCard USA consultant will be in touch soon to discuss the ways we can support your business.
BankCard USA will never share or sell your information.
×
CLICK SUBMIT And Start Saving
Just fill out the form below with
ZERO RISK and NO OBLIGATION
A BankCard USA consultant will be in touch soon to discuss the ways we can support your business.
[recaptcha]
BankCard USA will never share or sell your information.
×
